[
    {
        "ID": 4745,
        "Name": "Clara Neumann",
        "Email": "clara.neumann@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915334567892",
        "PostalCode": "50667",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": true,
        "Success": true,
        "FunnelID": "3",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Vollzeit",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Grundlegend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Keine Englischkenntnisse",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    },
    {
        "ID": 4233,
        "Name": "David Schulz",
        "Email": "david.schulz@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915445678903",
        "PostalCode": "80331",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": false,
        "Success": true,
        "FunnelID": "1",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "CE",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Vollzeit",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Grundlegend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Keine Englischkenntnisse",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    },
    {
        "ID": 42306,
        "Name": "Felix Meier",
        "Email": "felix.meier@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915667890125",
        "PostalCode": "01067",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": false,
        "Success": false,
        "FunnelID": "2",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Vollzeit",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Grundlegend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Keine Englischkenntnisse",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    },
    {
        "ID": 3145,
        "Name": "Clara Neumann",
        "Email": "clara.neumann@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915334567892",
        "PostalCode": "50667",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": true,
        "Success": true,
        "FunnelID": "3",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "C1E",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Teilzeit (20h)",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Grundlegend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Keine Englischkenntnisse",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    },
    {
        "ID": 41123,
        "Name": "Ross Schulz",
        "Email": "david.schulz@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915445678903",
        "PostalCode": "80331",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": false,
        "Success": true,
        "FunnelID": "1",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "CE",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Vollzeit",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Fließend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Basic",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    },
    {
        "ID": 61543,
        "Name": "Felo Meier",
        "Email": "felix.meier@example.com",
        "Phone": "+4915667890125",
        "PostalCode": "01067",
        "IsTalent": true,
        "IsHired": false,
        "Success": false,
        "FunnelID": "2",
        "FormInfo": [
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "B",
                "question": "Führerschein"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Minijob",
                "question": "Arbeitsmodell"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Tieflader",
                "question": "Fahrzeugtyp"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Mischverkehr",
                "question": "Verkehrsart"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "FQN"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Nein",
                "question": "ADR"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Grundlegend",
                "question": "Deutsch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Incorrect",
                "answers": "Fluent",
                "question": "Englisch"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Ja",
                "question": "Wochenendarbeit"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "test",
                "question": "Ihre Verfügbarkeit?"
            },
            {
                "result": "Correct",
                "answers": "Morgens 8:00 - 12:00 Uhr",
                "question": "Kontaktzeit"
            }
        ],
        "CreatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z",
        "UpdatedAt": "2025-05-05T13:40:07.558845Z"
    }
]